<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[gsub("nick prokesch", "unregex")]]></title>
  <link href="http://nickprokesch.nfshost.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://nickprokesch.nfshost.com/"/>
  <updated>2012-10-30T17:25:47-04:00</updated>
  <id>http://nickprokesch.nfshost.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Nick Prokesch]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enable Siri Omnifocus Iphone 4]]></title>
    <link href="http://nickprokesch.nfshost.com/blog/2012/10/30/enable-siri-omnifocus-iphone-4/"/>
    <updated>2012-10-30T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://nickprokesch.nfshost.com/blog/2012/10/30/enable-siri-omnifocus-iphone-4</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Back in April, <a href="http://www.idownloadblog.com/2012/04/14/how-to-enable-omnifocus-siri-reminders-on-iphone-4/">I wrote about how to enable Reminders capture for OmniFocus on the iPhone 4</a>, and other devices without Siri. That particular method required a jailbroken iPhone with iFile installed, and involved modifying OmniFocus&#8217; Info.plist file.</p>

<p>Yesterday, <a href="http://www.macstories.net/links/change-default-sync-times-of-omnifocus-for-mac-and-ios/">Federico posted an interesting article</a> on changing some hidden app values in OmniFocus, both on the Mac and on iOS. This tidbit suggested that these debug values in the Info.plist file could actually be changed via an OmniFocus URL scheme without a jailbreak. I did a little testing, and I was able to get Reminders integration working on my non-jailbroken iPhone 4 running iOS 6 with the latest version of OmniFocus for iPhone.</p>

<p>Simply copy and paste these URLs into Safari, one at a time, and launch them.</p>

<ul>
<li>x-omnifocus-debug:set-default:DebugEnableSiriOverride:1</li>
<li>x-omnifocus-debug:set-default:DebugSiriCapture:1</li>
</ul>


<p>They will open OmniFocus, ask if you want to invoke the commands, and then quit the app. After launching both URLs, and reopening OmniFocus, I found the Reminders section in my OmniFocus settings. After a brief test, I confirmed Reminders capture to be fully working.</p>

<p>What other fun flags are there in OmniFocus? Can we get some experimental features working? I fear that Federico has opened Pandora&#8217;s box for me, and that I am about to have the most unproductive work week. Thanks.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
